ever.com 2017-04-25

# Privacy Policy — Ever

## Everalbum Inc. Privacy Policy

 **Last Modified: November 1st, 2016**

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. For this reason, Everalbum Inc. focuses on providing the best service to you while keeping your information as private as possible.

This Privacy Policy provides our policies and procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. Users can access the Everalbum Inc. service (the "Service") through our website www.ever.com, our applications on Devices, through APIs, and through third-parties. A "Device" is any computer used to access the Ever Service, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic device. This Privacy Policy governs your access of the Ever Service, regardless of how you access it, and by using our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy.

### Information Collection & Use Practices

We may collect and store the following personal information when running the Ever Service:

 _ **Information You Provide**_. When you register an account, we collect some personal information, such as your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses. You may provide us with your contacts' email addresses, phone numbers, or other contact information when sharing folders or files with them through the Service. We may also receive Personal Information (including, for example, your email address or phone number) through other users, for example if they have tried to share something with you or tried to refer Ever to you.

 _ **Files and Content.**_  We collect and store the files you upload, download, or access with the Ever Service ("Files"). If you add a file to your Ever that has been previously uploaded by you or another user, we may associate all or a portion of the previous file with your account rather than storing a duplicate. When you share photos, videos or other content to the Service, we will also collect information about the content, such as the time, date and location the photo or content was taken or uploaded, (also known as metadata), and how you use them, who views them or with whom you share. 

 _ **Address Book Information.**_  With your permission, Ever may access your contact list available on your mobile device or in your email accounts so that you may share files or folders with your friends, or invite others to join the Ever Service. When you invite others to join Ever by using our referral page, we send a one-time text message on your behalf to that referral. You may share files or folders with friends from the Service by a variety of ways, including via text or email (sent by Ever or by your native device program), on social media or messaging services. We do not use your contact list information for any purpose other than to send invitations or messages on your behalf and with your explicit consent. We also do not store your address book information on our servers.

 _ **Third Party Site Information.**_   When you connect Ever to your social media accounts or third party sites or services, such as Facebook, Instagram, Amazon, Dropbox and others, we may receive information from those services including your profile information, photos and videos, friends and contact lists, user name, user ID associated with your third party account, age range, language, country, and any other information you permit the social network to share with third parties. The data we receive is dependent upon your privacy settings with the third party site or social network, and we will not post information about you on third party social media sites without your consent. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our Service.  

We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, as well as to communicate directly with you, such as to send you email messages and push notifications, and permit you to communicate with others on the Service or on social media or invite others to join the Service.  We may also use information about your activities on the Service to provide personalized content, including targeted advertising.  We may also send you Service-related emails or messages (e.g., account verification, change or updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices).  For more information about your communication preferences, see “Your Choices Regarding Your Information” below.

 _ **Information We Collect Automatically Through the Use of Technology.**_  When you visit our website or use our mobile apps, we and our third party business partners may collect certain information about your computer or device through tracking technology such as cookies, web beacons, log files, or other tracking/recording tools. The information we collect through the use of tracking technologies includes, but is not limited to, IP address, browser information, referring/exit pages and URLs, click stream data and information about how you interact with links on the website, mobile app, or Service, domain names, landing pages, page views, cookie data that allows us to uniquely identify your browser and track your browsing behavior on our site other persistent identifiers. Some or all of this data may be combined with other personally identifying information described above. When you access our Service by or through a mobile device, we may receive or collect and store a unique identification numbers associated with your device or our mobile application (including, for example, a UDID, Unique ID for Advertisers (“IDFA”), Google Ad ID, or Windows Advertising ID or other identifier), mobile carrier, device type, model and manufacturer, mobile device operating system brand and model, phone number, and, depending on your mobile device settings, your geographical location data, including GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude), WiFi location or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device. We use this information to (i) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site or mobile app, (ii) provide custom, personalized content and information, including advertising, (iii) monitor the effectiveness of our Service and our marketing campaigns, (iv) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, users, traffic, and demographic patterns, (v) diagnose or fix technology problems, and (vi) automatically update our mobile application on your system and related devices.

We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other information that assists us in analyzing and improving the Service. Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our users, we are not able to respond to Do Not Track signals from your browser at this time. 

### Information Sharing

 _ **Your Use.  **_We will display your Personal Information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Service according to the preferences you set in your account. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want others to know about you. Please consider carefully what information you disclose in your profile page and your desired level of anonymity. You can review and revise your profile information at any time. We do not sell your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may also share or disclose your information with your consent, for example if you use a third party application to access your account (see below). Through certain features of the Service, you may also have the ability to make some of your information public. Public information may be broadly and quickly disseminated.

 _ **Service Providers, Business Partners and Others.**_  We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service's features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Amazon's S3 storage service to store some of your information (for example, your Files). You can find more information on Amazon's data security from the S3 site or, read more about how Everalbum Inc. and Amazon securely store data.

 _ **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Everalbum Inc.'s Rights.**_  We may disclose to parties outside Everalbum Inc. files stored in your Ever and information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Ever, its users, or others; or (d) to protect Everalbum Inc.'s property rights. If we provide your Ever files to a law enforcement agency as set forth above, we will remove Everalbum Inc.'s encryption from the files before providing them to law enforcement. However, Everalbum Inc. will not be able to decrypt any files that you encrypted prior to storing them on Ever.

 _ **Business Transfers.  **_If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction. We will use our best efforts to ensure that you are notified (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your Personal Information or Files, or if either become subject to a different Privacy Policy, and of any choices you may have regarding your information.

 _ **Anonymized or Non-Personal Information.**_  We may disclose information with others in an aggregated or anonymous form that does not reasonably identify you as an individual.

### Your Choices Regarding Your Information

 _ **Modifying Your Information and Settings:**_  You may modify your account information, update or amend your personal information, control in-app notifications, or change your password at any time by logging in to your account or contacting us at privacy@ever.com. You can also stop receiving promotional email communications from us by clicking on the “unsubscribe link” provided in such communications. We make every effort to promptly process all unsubscribe requests. You may not opt out of Service-related communications (e.g., account verification, change or updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). If you have any questions about reviewing or modifying your account information, you can contact us directly at privacy@ever.com.

### Data Storage

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please email us at privacy@ever.com. We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your information quickly upon request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion. In addition, we do not delete from our servers files that you have in common with other users. 

### Security and Storage of Information

Ever cares about the security of your information and uses commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information we collect.  However, no security system is impenetrable and we cannot guarantee the security of our systems 100%.  In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Ever or our subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities.  If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Ever or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.  

### Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@ever.com](mailto:privacy@ever.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will take steps to delete such information from our files.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@ever.com](mailto:privacy@ever.com).
